Guide to the Riverwalk Jazz Collection ARS.0129
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Program recordings
  - 291. Beautiful Changes: The Whiteman Years, Giordano, Vince; Stein, Andy
    With guests Vince Giordano and Andy Stein.
    Paul Whiteman Orchestra.; Whiteman, Paul, 1890-1967
    - Beautiful Changes: Whiteman Tunes, 2007-03-19; 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Beautiful Changes. #17. Revised Master, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Beautiful Changes. #24, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 292. Jimmy McPartland at 100: Hot Jazz and Good Times, Barnard, Bob
    With guest Bob Barnard. Aired without "at 100" reference for 7/2011 broadcast.
    McPartland, Jimmy, 1907-1991
    - Jimmy McPartland at 100: Interviews; Tunes, 8 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Jimmy McPartland at 100. #21, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Jimmy McPartland: Hot Jazz and Good Times. #36, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Jimmy McPartland: Hot Jazz and Good Times. #30, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 293. Irving Berlin's Music Box, Ferro, Nina; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-
    - Irving Berlin's Music Box. #22, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 294. James P. Johnson: The Supreme Tickler, Bagneris, Vernel; Berg, Shelly
    With guests Vernel Bagneris and Shelly Berg.
    - James P. Johnson: The Supreme Tickler. #24, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - James P. Johnson: The Supreme Tickler.#8, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - James P. Johnson: The Supreme Tickler. #20, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 295. Keyboard Wizard: The Genius of Art Tatum, Bagneris, Vernel; Berg, Shelly
    Tatum, Art, 1909-1956
    - Keyboard Wizard. #29, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Keyboard Wizard. #21, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Keyboard Wizard. #41, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Keyboard Wizard. #3, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 296. Symphony in Riffs: Centennial Celebration for Benny Carter, Berger, Ed; Carter, Benny
    With guest Benny Carter. Centennial reference removed from 2008 show. 2012 show titled "When Lights are Low: A Conversation on Benny Carter with Biographer Ed Berger." See also original program from 1992, "I'm In the Mood for Swing: A Tribute to the Life and Music of Benny Carter" (#33).
    - Symphony in Riffs: Ed Berger Interview; Ed Berger Clips; Tune Rundown and Interviews; HRs, 7 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Centennial Celebration for Benny Carter. #30, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Symphony in Riffs: Celebrating Benny Carter. #17, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - When Lights are Low: A Conversation on Benny Carter with Biographer Ed Berger. #17, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 297. Jamming on the 88s: An Evening with Piano Virtuoso Shelly Berg, Berg, Shelly
    With guest Shelly Berg. Also aired as "Sweet Thunder: Piano Virtuoso Shelly Berg and The Jim Cullum Jazz Band."
    - Shelly Interview, 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
    - Jamming on the 88s. #33, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Sweet Thunder: Piano Virtuoso Shelly Berg and The Jim Cullum Jazz Band. #28, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Sweet Thunder: Piano Virtuoso Shelly Berg and The Jim Cullum Jazz Band. #21, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Sweet Thunder: Piano Virtuoso Shelly Berg and The Jim Cullum Jazz Band. #36, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 298. Crescent City Stomp: A Post Katrina Celebration of New Orleans Jazz, Bagneris, Vernel; Barnard, Bob; Chapman, Topsy; Christopher, Evan; Sheridan, John, pianist
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Topsy Chapman, Bob Barnard, Evan Christopher and John Sheridan. Original version of program, "Crescent City Stomp Off" (#261) never aired.
    - Crescent City Stomp: A Celebtration of New Orleans Jazz. #36, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 299. Gennett Records: The Little Studio That Could, Christopher, Evan; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon; Payton, Nicholas; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Evan Christopher, Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, Dick Hyman and Nicholas Payton.
    Starr Piano Company. Gennett Record Division.
    - Gennett Records. #37, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Gennett Records. #42, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Gennett Records. #45, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 300. Unsung Songwriters: The Great Craftsmen, Baker, Clint; Barnard, Bob; Barrett, Dan; Ferro, Nina; Giordano, Vince; Havens, Bob; Heitger, Duke; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Oakley, Leon; Sheridan, John, pianist; Vaché, Allan
    With guests Nina Ferro, Dick Hyman, Rebecca Kilgore, Allan Vaché, John Sheridan, Vince Giordano, Bob Barnard, Duke Heitger, Clint Baker, Leon Oakley, Dan Barrett and Bob Havens.
    Ahlert, Fred A., 1892-1953; Brooks, Shelton; Creamer, Henry, 1879-1930; Daniels, Charles N. (Charles Neil), 1878-1943; Kalmar, Bert, 1884-1947; Layton, Turner, 1894-1978; Ruby, Harry; Turk, Roy, 1892-1934; Woods, Harry, 1896-1970; Young, Joe, 1889-1939
    - Unsung Songwriters. #39, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Unsung Songwriters. #19, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 301. Riverboats, Roustabouts and Jazz: Life on the Mississippi, Bagneris, Vernel; Christopher, Evan; Edison, Harry, 1915-1999; Giordano, Vince; Grosz, Marty; Oakley, Leon; Stein, Andy; Walbridge, Mike; Woods, Carol
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, Carol Woods, Marty Grosz, Andy Stein, Harry "Sweets" Edison, Vince Giordano, and Evan Christopher.
    - Riverboats, Roustabouts and Jazz: Tunes, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Riverboats, Roustabouts and Jazz. #42, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Riverboats, Roustabouts and Jazz. #29, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Riverboats, Roustabouts and Jazz. #28, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 302. One Hit Wonders of the Golden Era, Allen, Harry, saxophonist; Hedges, Chuck; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Vaché, Allan
    With guests Harry Allen, Dick Hyman, Chuck Hedges and Alan Vaché.
    Burnett, Ernie, 1884-1959; Burwell, Cliff, 1898-1976; Coburn, Richard, 1886-1952; Hubbell, John Raymond, 1879-1954; Shavers, Charlie, 1917-1971
    - One Hit Wonders of the Golden Era: Tune Rundown, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - One Hit Wonders of the Golden Era. #43, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - One Hit Wonders of the Golden Era. #2, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - One Hit Wonders of the Golden Era. #35, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 303. A Woman's Touch: Celebrating Women Composers in Jazz, Chapman, Topsy; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Nakasian, Stephanie; Woods, Carol
    With guests Topsy Chapman, Carol Woods, Stephanie Nakasian and Rebecca Kilgore.
    Fitzgerald, Ella; Friedman, Leo, 1869-1927; Holiner, Mann; Humes, Helen; Nichols, Alberta, 1898-1957; Rainey, Ma, 1886-1939; Swift, Kay, 1897-1993; Whitson, Beth Slater, 1879-1930
    - Woman's Touch: Tune Rundown, 1 CD-R (Audio 89)
    - Woman's Touch: #45, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Woman's Touch. #40, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Woman's Touch. #9, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 304. Nice Work If You Can Get It: A Gershwin Cabaret, Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    - Nice Work If You Can Get It: Tune Rundown, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Nice Work If You Can Get It. #48, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Nice Work If You Can Get It. #48, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Nice Work If You Can Get It. #48, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 305. Gems from the Cutting Room Floor: A Treasury of Newly Discovered Riverwalk Jazz Tracks, Giordano, Vince; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    - Tune Rundowns, 5 CD-Rs (Audio 134)
    - Gems from the Cutting Room Floor. #51, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 306. A New Generation: The Jim Cullum Jazz Band and Clarinet Virtuoso Dave Bennett, Bennett, Dave, 1984-
    With guest Dave Bennett.
    - New Generation: Rehearsal, 2007-11-28; 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - New Generation. #52, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - New Generation. #41, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - New Generation. #38, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 307. In the Footsteps of Giants: Introducing Trumpet Dynamo Bria Skonberg, Skonberg, Bria
    With guest Bria Skonberg.
    - Bria Samples; Bria Interview; Rehearsal, 4 CD-Rs (Audio 134)
    - In the Footsteps of Giants. #3, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - In the Footsteps of Giants. #33, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - In the Footsteps of Giants. #18, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 308. Keeping It Hot: The Jim Cullum Jazz Band with Trumpeter Bria Skonberg, Clarinetist Dave Bennett and Drummer Michael Waskiewicz, Bennett, Dave, 1984-; Skonberg, Bria; Waskiewicz, Michael
    With guests Bria Skonberg, Dave Bennett and Michael Waskiewicz.
    - Keeping It Hot. #4, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Keeping It Hot. #10, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 309. Hearts Afire: A Riverwalk Jazz Valentine, Bagneris, Vernel; Chapman, Topsy; Ferro, Nina; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Pizzarelli, John; Woods, Carol
    Other Finding Aids note
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Rebecca Kilgore, Nina Ferro, Topsy Chapman, Carol Woods, and John Pizzarelli.
    - Hearts Afire. #7, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 310. The Test of Time: A Century of Song, Barnard, Bob; Chapman, Topsy; Davern, Kenny; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Bob Barnard, Mike Walbridge, Kenny Davern, and Topsy Chapman.
    - Test of Time. #9, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Test of Time. #50, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Test of Time. #30, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 311. Blues Queens, Cakewalkin' Babies and Songbirds, Woods, Carol
    - Blues Queens, Cakewalkin' Babies and Songbirds: Old Show; Rundown; Billie Holiday Replacement, 3 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Blues Queens, Cakewalkin' Babies and Songbirds. #10, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Blues Queens, Cakewalkin' Babies and Songbirds. #9, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 312. Lester Leaps In: The President of Tenor Sax, Bagneris, Vernel; Chapman, Topsy; Edison, Harry, 1915-1999; Peplowski, Ken
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Topsy Chapman, Harry "Sweets" Edison, and Ken Peplowski.
    Young, Lester, 1909-1959
    - Lester Leaps In: Tune Rundown, 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Lester Leaps In. #12 Revised, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Lester Leaps In. #6, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Lester Leaps In. #34, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 313. Talking Trumpet with Clark Terry, Terry, Clark
    Terry, Clark
    - Talking Trumpet with Clark Terry: Interview By David Holt; Rundown, 3 CD-Rs (Audio 89)
    - Talking Trumpet with Clark Terry.#15, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Talking Trumpet with Clark Terry. #9, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Talking Trumpet with Clark Terry: Stll Active On His 90th Birthday. #49, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 314. Riverwalk Jazz Hall of Fame: Legends at The Landing, Cheatham, Doc; Haggart, Bob; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999
    With guests Bob Haggart, Joe Williams, and Doc Cheatham.
    - Riverwalk Jazz Hall of Fame: Web Clips; Rundown, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Riverwalk Jazz Hall of Fame. #16, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 315. Sophisticated Ladies and Red Hot Mammas, Chapman, Topsy; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Topsy Chapman and Dick Hyman.
    - Sophisticated Ladies and Red Hot Mammas. #19, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Sophisticated Ladies and Red Hot Mammas, #30, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 316. Goodman, Shaw and Dorsey: Big Band Leaders and Their Small Combos, Gordon, Bobby; Hampton, Lionel; Ogilvie, Brian; Peplowski, Ken; Sheridan, John, pianist; Vaché, Allan
    With guests Ken Peplowski, John Sheridan, Brian Ogilvie, Lionel Hampton, Allen Vaché, Bobby Gordon and Harry Allen.
    Benny Goodman Quartet.; Clambake Seven (Musical group).; Dorsey, Tommy, 1905-1956; Goodman, Benny, 1909-1986; Gramercy Five.; Shaw, Artie, 1910-2004
    - Goodman, Shaw and Dorsey: Band Within A Band Tune Rundown, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Goodman, Shaw and Dorsey. #24, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Goodman, Shaw and Dorsey. #43, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Goodman, Shaw and Dorsey. #31, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 317. A Night at Nick's: Hot Jazz in the Big Apple, Barnard, Bob; Davern, Kenny; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Ogilvie, Brian; Peplowski, Ken; Wilber, Bob
    With guests Kenny Davern, Dick Hyman, Ken Peplowski, Bob Barnard, Bob Wilber and Brian Ogilvie.
    - Nick's Webclips 6/16, 1 CD-R (Audio 89)
    - Night at Nick's: interviews, 2008; 13 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Night at Nick's: Dixieland Outpost in the Big Apple. #26, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Night at Nick's. #36, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Night at Nick's. #48, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 318. Riverwalk Jazz BBQ: The Lazy Days of Summer, Bagneris, Vernel; Cusack, Kim; Gordon, Bobby; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Kellso, Jon-Erik; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Pittsley, Mike; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999
    With guests Bobby Gordon, Kim Cusack, Vernel Bagneris, Joe Williams, Dick Hyman, Mike Pittsley, Rebecca Kilgore, and Jon-Erik Kellso.
    - Riverwalk Jazz BBQ. #27, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Riverwalk Jazz BBQ. #26, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 319. Re-creating Black Vaudeville with Broadway's Vernel Bagneris, Bagneris, Vernel; Chapman, Topsy; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Topsy Chapman, and Dick Hyman.
    - Re-creating Black Vaudeville with Broadway's Vernel Bagneris. #31, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 320. Slipping and Sliding: Jazz Trombone at Its Best, Allred, Bill; Barrett, Dan; Havens, Bob; Phillips, Russ, trombonist
    With guests Bob Havens, Dan Barrett, Russ Phillips and Bill Allred.
    - Slipping and Sliding: Rundown; Tunes, 3 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Slipping and Sliding. #33, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Slipping and Sliding. #22, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 321. Clarinet Marmalade: Hot Jazz to Smooth Ballads, Christopher, Evan; Cusack, Kim; Davern, Kenny; Peplowski, Ken; Vaché, Allan; Wilber, Bob
    With guests Ken Peplowski, Evan Christopher, Allan Vaché, Kenny Davern, Kim Cusack and Bob Wilber.
    - Clarinet Marmalade: Hot Jazz to Smooth Ballads. #35, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Clarinet Marmalade: Hot Jazz to Smooth Ballads. #42, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 322. Women of the Harlem Renaissance, Berg, Shelly; Caceres, David; Cuesta, Henry; Frigo, John, 1916-2007; Wilber, Bob
    With guests Shelly Berg, Bob Wilber, David Caceres, Johnny Frigo, and Henry Cuesta.
    - Women of the Harlem Renaissance. #39, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Women of the Harlem Renaissance. #5, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 323. A Triple Crown of Tunesmiths: Youmans, Barris and Green, Berg, Shelly; Campesi, Sebastian; Carter, Benny; Grosz, Marty; Payton, Nicholas; Peplowski, Ken; Salas, Alfredo; Woods, Carol
    With guests Carol Woods, Dick Hyman, Ken Peplowski, Marty Grosz, Nicholas Payton, Benny Carter, Alfredo Salas, Shelly Berg, Topsy Chapman, John Sheridan and Sebastian Campesi.
    Barris, Harry, 1905-1962; Green, Johnny, 1908-1989; Youmans, Vincent, 1898-1946
    - Triple Crown of Tunesmiths: Tunes; Session, 2008-10-23; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Triple Crown of Tunesmiths. #43, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Triple Crown of Tunesmiths. [#19], 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 324. Two of a Kind: Swinging Duos at The Landing, Chapman, Topsy; Grosz, Marty; Oakley, Leon; Payton, Nicholas; Stein, Andy; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Marty Grosz, Nicholas Payton, Mike Walbridge, Topsy Chapman, Leon Oakley, and Andy Stein.
    - Two of a Kind: Tune Rundown; Grosz and Stein Segment; Leon/Mike, 5 CD-Rs (Audio 89)
    - Two of a Kind. #46, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 325. Hot Licks and Sweet Things: A Tour of San Francisco's Barbary Coast, Bagneris, Vernel; Barnard, Bob; Chapman, Topsy; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Topsy Chapman, Vernel Bagneris, Bob Barnard, Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, and Dick Hyman.
    Le Protti, Sid
    - Tunes; Sid LeProtti; Barbary Coast Must-Haves, 5 CD-Rs (Audio 134)
    - Hot Licks and Sweet Things. #49, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Hot Licks and Sweet Things. #37, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 326. New Orleans Jazz Pioneers and Their Legacy, Christopher, Evan; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon; Walbridge, Mike
    With guests Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, Dick Hyman and Evan Christopher.
    - New Orleans Jazz Pioneers and Their Legacy: HRs; Tune Evaluation; Snoozer Quinn; Rundown; Jim Interviews Jazz Pioneers; David Holt Narration, 6 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - New Orleans Jazz Pioneers and Their Legacy. #51, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - New Orleans Jazz Pioneers and Their Legacy. #16, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 327. Songstress Nina Ferro: Live in Concert with The Jim Cullum Jazz Band, Cuesta, Henry; Ferro, Nina; Frigo, John, 1916-2007; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Ogilvie, Brian
    With guests Nina Ferro, Dick Hyman, Brian Ogilvie, Johnny Frigo, and Henry Cuesta.
    - Songstress Nina Ferro: Rundown; Band Only, 2008; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Songstress Nina Ferro. #52, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Songstress Nina Ferro. #51, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 328. NYC All-Stars and a New Year's Jam, Barrett, Dan; Cheatham, Doc; Grosz, Marty; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Nakasian, Stephanie; Woods, Carol
    With guests Carol Woods, Stephanie Nakasian, Dick Hyman, Doc Cheatham, Dan Barrett, and Marty Grosz.
    - NYC All-Stars and a New Year's Jam. #1, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 329. Swinging on V-Disc: Jazz in WWII, Allen, Harry, saxophonist; Bagneris, Vernel; Barnard, Bob; Edison, Harry, 1915-1999; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Pizzarelli, John; Terry, Clark; Vaché, Allan
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Harry Allen, Allan Vaché, Dick Hyman, Bob Barnard, John Pizzarelli, Clark Terry, and Harry "Sweets" Edison.
    - Swinging on V-Disc. #4, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Swinging on V-Disc. #18, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Swinging on V-Disc. #43, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 330. Ebony Love Songs: A Celebration of Black Songwriters, Bagneris, Vernel; Baker, Clint; Barnard, Bob; Chapman, Topsy; Cuesta, Henry; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Nakasian, Stephanie; Schultz, Bob; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999; Woods, Carol
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Topsy Chapman, Dick Hyman, Clint Baker, Stephanie Nakasian, Carol Woods, Joe Williams, Bob Schultz, Henry Cuesta and Bob Barnard.
    - RW07 Mix 1 Ebony Love Songs, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Ebony Love Songs: Rundown, Tunes, 5 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Ebony Love Songs. #7, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Ebony Love Songs. #6, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 331. A Night at Bricktop's: Jazz in 1930s' Montmartre, Bagneris, Vernel; Berg, Shelly; Chapman, Topsy; Mehling, Paul
    With guests Topsy Chapman, Vernel Bagneris, Paul Mehling, and Shelly Berg.
    Bricktop, 1894-1984
    - Night at Bricktop's. #13, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Night at Bricktop's. #40, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Night at Bricktop's. #39, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 332. Benny Goodman Swinging at 100: A Centenary Celebration, Allen, Harry, saxophonist; Bennett, Dave, 1984-; Cheatham, Doc; Cocuzzi, John; Hampton, Lionel; Hedges, Chuck; Salas, Alfredo; Sheridan, John, pianist; Vaché, Allan
    With guests Allan Vaché, Alfredo Salas, Doc Cheatham, Dave Bennett, John Cocuzzi, John Sheridan, Lionel Hampton, Harry Allen, and Chuck Hedges.
    - Benny Goodman Swinging at 100. #17, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 333. Remembering Ralph Sutton: Long Way From St. Louis, Sutton, Ralph, 1922-2001
    - Remembering Ralph Sutton. #18, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Remembering Ralph Sutton. #28, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 334. Wrap Your Cares in Rhythm: A Concert of Recession-Proof Tunes, Bagneris, Vernel; Chapman, Topsy; Christopher, Evan; Ferro, Nina; Gibson, Banu; Glover, Savion; Haggart, Bob; Hedges, Chuck; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Lawson, Yank; Nakasian, Stephanie; Phillips, Russ, trombonist; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Topsy Chapman, Evan Christopher, Nina Ferro, Banu Gibson, Savion Glover, Bob Haggart, Dick Hyman, Yank Lawson, Stephanie Nakasian, Russ Phillips, and Joe Williams.
    - Wrap Your Cares in Rhythm: Tunes; Spare Parts, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 89)
    - Wrap Your Troubles in Rhythm. #21, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 335. Swinging the Band: The Pops Foster Story, Barnard, Bob; Payton, Nicholas
    With guests Nicholas Payton and Bob Barnard.
    Foster, Pops, 1892-1969
    - Swinging the Band. #22, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Swinging the Band. #7, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 336. Jazz Daddies: A Father's Day Celebration, Barnard, Bob; Berg, Shelly; Chapman, Topsy; Cocuzzi, John; Hampton, Lionel; Payton, Nicholas; Pizzarelli, Bucky; Pizzarelli, John
    With guests Bob Barnard, Shelley Berg, Topsy Chapman, John Cocuzzi, Lionel Hampton, Nicholas Payton, Bucky Pizzarelli and John Pizzarelli.
    - My Sweet Papa's Voice. #25, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Jazz Daddies: A Jazz Celebration For Dad. #24, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
    - Jim, Jazz Daddies Q.1; Fathers Day Clips, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 134)
  - 337. Come Rain or Come Shine: Johnny Mercer - 100 Years, 1000 Songs, Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Kellso, Jon-Erik; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Nakasian, Stephanie; Sheridan, John, pianist; Woods, Carol
    With guests Rebecca Kilgore, Carol Woods, Dick Hyman, John Sheridan, Jon-Erik Kellso, and Stephanie Nakasian. 2010 program titled "Come Rain or Come Shine: Johnny Mercer, Master of Popular Song."
    - Come Rain or Come Shine: Mercer Clips Edit 1, 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Come Rain or Come Shine. #26, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Come Rain or Come Shine. #44, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Come Rain or Come Shine: Johnny Mercer In His Own Words. #22, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 338. At the Jazz Band Ball: Jazz Classics Live from the Stanford Jazz Workshop, Christopher, Evan
    With guest Evan Christopher. Recorded at the Stanford Jazz Workshop. See also Stanford recordings.
    - At the Jazz Band Ball: Jazz Classics Live from the Stanford Jazz Workshop. #29, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - At the Jazz Band Ball: Jazz Classics Live from the Stanford Jazz Workshop. #26, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 339. Turk and Lu: West Coast Classic Jazz in Concert
    See also "West Coast Classic Jazz: A Tribute to Turk Murphy and Lu Waters" (#41) and Stanford recordings.
    - Turk and Lu: Tunes, 2009-06-16; 1 CD-R (Audio 89)
    - Turk and Lu. #30, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Turk and Lu. #33, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 340. Melancholy Blues: The Story of Clarinetist Johnny Dodds, Christopher, Evan; Davern, Kenny; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Peplowski, Ken
    With guests Evan Christopher, Dick Hyman, Ken Peplowsi, and Kenny Davern.
    Dodds, Johnny, 1892-1940
    - Melancholy Blues: Rundown; Tunes, 3 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Melancholy Blues. #37, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Melancholy Blues. #5, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 341. The Rise and Fall of Joe 'King' Oliver
    - Rise and Fall of Joe 'King' Oliver. #39, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Rise and Fall of Joe 'King' Oliver. #13, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 342. Diga Diga Do: Jazz Standards of Jimmy McHugh, Allen, Harry, saxophonist; Chapman, Topsy; Ferro, Nina; Glover, Savion; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Mehling, Paul; Vaché, Allan
    With guests Allan Vaché, Rebecca Kilgore, Harry Allen, Topsy Chapman, Nina Ferro and Savion Glover.
    McHugh, Jimmy, 1894-1969
    - Diga Diga Do: Clips and Tunes, 5 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Diga Diga Do. #42, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Diga Diga Do. #42, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 343. Fats, Hoagy and W.C. Handy: 20 Years of Riverwalk Jazz, Bagneris, Vernel; Berg, Shelly; Chapman, Topsy; Hockett, Ron
    With guests Topsy Chapman, Vernel Bagneris, Ron Hockett and Shelly Berg.
    Carmichael, Hoagy, 1899-1981; Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1873-1958; Waller, Fats, 1904-1943
    - Fats, Hoagy and W.C. Handy. #44, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Fats, Hoagy and W.C. Handy. #29, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 344. Chicago's Jazz Age Melting Pot: Hot Jazz, Boogie Woogie and the Blues, Berg, Shelly; Chapman, Topsy; Doyle, Johnathan; Hockett, Ron; Jellema, David; Pearl Stable.
    With guests Topsy Chapman, Ron Hockett, Shelly Berg, Johnathan Doyle and David Jellema. See also Pearl Stable recordings.
    - Chicago's Jazz Age Melting Pot. Live At Pearl Stable. #47, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Chicago's Jazz Age Melting Pot. #15, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)